♪Drink frost♪
♪프로스트를 마셔보세요♪
♪Hold tight to your roots♪
♪뿌리를 단단히 잡으세요♪
♪This land♪
♪이 땅♪
♪Chasing the Waves♪
♪파도를 쫓아♪
♪My leaves blow past♪
♪나의 나뭇잎이 지나간다♪
♪The Border of Ten Thousand Miles♪
♪만리의 경계♪
♪Looking at each other far away♪
♪멀리서 서로를 바라보며♪
♪At the other end is♪
♪다른 쪽 끝에는 ♪
♪Forever and ever♪
♪영원히 영원히♪
♪When we meet and say goodbye♪
♪만나서 이별할 때♪
♪When you're snuggled away♪
♪당신이 껴안고 있을 때♪
♪I never forget♪
♪절대 잊지 않아요♪
♪The Shadow of the Lightsaber♪
♪광선검의 그림자♪
♪Draw through the blemishes of the sky♪
♪하늘의 흠집을 뚫고 나아가세요♪
♪Ok Dream♪
♪좋아 꿈♪
♪Broken in the wind♪
♪바람에 부서지네♪
♪Beat the wind and surf♪
♪바람을 이겨내고 서핑을 즐겨보세요♪
♪Watch thousands of ships crossing over♪
♪수천 척의 배가 건너가는 모습을 감상하세요♪
♪The sea and rice fields change♪
♪바다와 논이 변한다♪
♪Military uniform, women's uniform, Loi Fong♪
♪군복, 여성복, 로이퐁♪
♪Once drank ice, blood didn't get cold, dreamed of exploring the Leyou fields♪
♪얼음을 마셔도 피가 식지 않아 레이유 평원을 탐험하는 꿈을 꾸었습니다♪
♪Wishing only you by my side♪
♪당신만 내 곁에 있기를 바라요♪
♪No offense to Saengwasan♪
♪생와산을 욕하지 마세요♪
♪Tree soaring to the sky, roots intertwined, traveling to the ends of the earth beside you♪
♪하늘을 향해 솟아오르는 나무, 뿌리가 얽혀 당신 곁에서 땅 끝까지 여행하는 나무♪
♪Look at the fireflies sitting on our shoulders♪
♪어깨 위에 앉은 반딧불을 보세요♪
♪No regrets in the mundane♪
♪세상에 후회는 없어♪
=The sky's love is close to my heart=
=하늘의 사랑이 내 마음에 가까이 있다=
=Episode 12=
=에피소드 12=
(Letter to Cui Lin)
(최린에게 보낸 편지)
The commander has returned.
지휘관이 돌아왔습니다.
sir
선생님
What is the situation in Yingzhou?
잉저우의 상황은 어떻습니까?
The commander's father suddenly became ill.
지휘관의 아버지가 갑자기 아프게 되었습니다.
There's nothing wrong with the seal.
씰에는 아무런 문제가 없습니다.
Tootsin recalled.
투신은 회상했다.
Tutsin was Father's confidant.
투신은 아버지의 절친한 친구였습니다.
He was attacked and injured along the way.
그는 도중에 공격을 받고 부상을 입었습니다.
After delivering the letter
편지를 전달한 후
He fell down and died.
그는 넘어져 죽었습니다.
sir
선생님
Sir, an old disease has recurred.
선생님, 오래된 질병이 재발했습니다.
Or were they poisoned?
아니면 중독됐나요?
It was not written in the letter.
편지에는 적혀 있지 않았습니다.
Sir, please allow me
선생님, 허락해주세요
Take the cavalry on a journey
기병대를 데리고 여행을 떠나세요
Go get help immediately.
즉시 가서 도움을 받으세요.
It was related to Father's safety.
아버지의 안전과 관련된 일이었습니다.
I will go with you.
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
cannot
할 수 없다
The army has a lot of baggage.
군대에는 짐이 많아요.
It's not convenient to move quickly.
빠르게 이동하는 것은 불편합니다.
It would be better for you to continue following the original plan.
원래 계획을 계속 따르는 것이 좋습니다.
Bring the army back to support quickly.
신속하게 지원을 위해 군대를 다시 데려오세요.
One more thing
하나 더
Your body has not yet recovered.
당신의 몸은 아직 회복되지 않았습니다.
urgent movement several days and nights in a row
며칠 밤낮 연속으로 긴급한 움직임
Your body won't be able to take it.
당신의 몸은 그것을 견딜 수 없을 것입니다.
Ah Ying, I've made up my mind.
아잉, 결심했어요.
you and me
너와 나
Take the cavalry to join together first.
기병을 데리고 먼저 합류하세요.
No need to argue anymore.
더 이상 논쟁할 필요가 없습니다.
can
~할 수 있다
Respect the Viceroy
총독을 존경하라
Saluting to the Viceroy
총독에게 경의를 표함
Your three children
당신의 세 자녀
After receiving the letter you wrote
당신이 쓴 편지를 받은 후
Li Jun and Li Lai were quite grateful.
Li Jun과 Li Lai는 매우 감사했습니다.
Hurry and promise to retreat immediately.
서둘러 즉시 후퇴하겠다고 약속하십시오.
Send the letter back
편지를 다시 보내세요
Please let me take good care of you.
제가 당신을 잘 돌볼 수 있게 해주세요.
As for Li
리의 경우
I couldn't imagine that he would slit his neck.
그 사람이 목을 자를 거라고는 상상도 못했어요.
Zheng Guogong's people then sent their heads back.
Zheng Guogong의 사람들은 고개를 돌려 보냈습니다.
(Letter to Viceroy Sun) Plus one letter attached.
(태양 총독에게 보내는 편지) 그리고 편지 한 통을 첨부합니다.
(I'm not the eldest son.)
(저는 큰 아들이 아닙니다.)
(If you kill your father)
(네가 아버지를 죽이면)
(I must thank you for being emperor.)
(황제가 되어주셔서 감사합니다.)
Li Ni called himself the emperor.
Li Ni는 자신을 황제라고 불렀습니다.
Of course, it must be inherited. Becoming Emperor after his real father
물론 상속받아야 합니다. 친아버지를 이어 황제가 됨
Prince Liang
리앙 왕자
This is a great auspicious matter.
이는 매우 경사스러운 일입니다.
If I have an idea
나에게 아이디어가 있다면
To betray like this
이렇게 배신하다니
Let the lightning strike
번개가 치자
You ungrateful son has slandered me.
당신 배은망덕한 아들이 나를 비방했습니다.
You ungrateful son, you are slandering me.
배은망덕한 아들아, 너는 나를 비방하고 있다.
The Viceroy is brilliant.
총독은 훌륭합니다.
Go call the royal doctor.
가서 왕실 의사에게 전화해 보세요.
See what happened.
무슨 일이 일어났는지 보세요.
Please accept it.
그것을 받아들이십시오.
Find a way to let Hu Yin Weiguo know.
Hu Yin Weiguo에게 알릴 방법을 찾으세요.
Yes, sir.
알겠습니다.
Viceroy
총독
Duke Liang's body had always been weak.
양공의 몸은 늘 약했다.
Plus he has heart arrhythmia.
게다가 그는 심장 부정맥을 앓고 있습니다.
Moments later, the mood turned violent.
잠시 후 분위기는 폭력적으로 변했다.
There are indications of cerebrovascular disease.
뇌혈관질환의 징후가 있습니다.
I'm afraid
나는 두려워
I fear that this disease will be a crisis.
이 질병이 위기가 될까봐 두렵습니다.
Can it help?
도움이 될까요?
I'm not sure.
잘 모르겠습니다.
Please take it away.
가져가주세요.
Take it easy.
진정하세요.
You have to take it easy.
당신은 진정해야합니다.
Don't let it hit.
부딪치지 마세요.
If you hit it, you'll run out of air.
부딪히면 공기가 부족해집니다.
Shi Chi Lang Shi Chi Lang
시치랑 시치랑
Urgent report from Luoyang
뤄양에서 긴급 보고
From the investigation of military scouts
군 정찰병 조사에서
Cavalry under Duke Linzhi
린치 공작 휘하의 기병
have abnormal movements
움직임이 이상하다
A detachment of cavalry carried heavy crossbows.
기병대는 무거운 석궁을 들고 다녔습니다.
Leave the Luo River unknown trace
루오강에 알려지지 않은 흔적을 남겨주세요
incorrect
잘못된
One cavalry soldier carried a heavy crossbow.
기병 병사 한 명이 무거운 석궁을 들고 있었습니다.
It's not like leaving Luoyang.
뤄양을 떠나는 것과는 다릅니다.
More like an ambush.
매복에 더 가깝습니다.
Who do they want to assassinate?
그들은 누구를 암살하고 싶어 하는가?
Enemy attacks
적의 공격
There's an enemy sneaking up on you.
당신에게 몰래 다가오는 적이 있습니다.
Sanlang
산랑
This time swept them clean and there was nothing left.
이번에는 그것들을 깨끗이 쓸어버렸고 아무것도 남지 않았습니다.
Cuilin
쿨린
I'll wait and see.
나는 기다려 볼 것이다.
This time you will still be alive.
이번에도 당신은 아직 살아있을 것입니다.
Survive or not?
살아남을 것인가 말 것인가?
sir
선생님
Chen thing
첸 것
Ah Ying
아잉
sir
선생님
Ah-ying Ah-ying
아잉 아잉
Please bear with me.
양해해 주시기 바랍니다.
How are you
어떻게 지내세요
kill
죽이다
wade
걸어 건너기
Can't go on.
계속할 수 없습니다.
The Zhenxi army has arrived.
Zhenxi 군대가 도착했습니다.
It's Li.
리입니다.
Li here came to help.
리가 도와주러 왔어.
what?
무엇?
Is it Li Ni again?
또 리니야?
sir
선생님
go
가다
Let me take a look at Cui Lin and Zhao He.
Cui Lin과 Zhao He를 살펴보겠습니다.
Or just run away?
아니면 그냥 도망칠까?
You shouldn't go looking for trouble with the Zhenxi Army.
Zhenxi 군대와 문제를 찾으러 가면 안됩니다.
The person Li Ni sent
리니가 보낸 사람
They were all excellent soldiers.
그들은 모두 훌륭한 군인들이었습니다.
Even if we can borrow soldiers
군인을 빌릴 수 있다고 해도
But it would be too damaging.
그러나 그것은 너무 해로울 것입니다.
We can't go and negotiate.
우리는 가서 협상할 수 없습니다.
Sanlang
산랑
As long as there is life
생명이 있는 한
There must be hope.
희망이 있어야합니다.
what happened
무슨 일이에요
Why did you bring her back?
왜 그녀를 다시 데려왔나요?
Hurry and call a military doctor.
서둘러 군 의사에게 전화하십시오.
fast
빠른
And are you injured or not?
그리고 부상을 입었나요, 안 다쳤나요?
The arrowhead went in too deep.
화살촉이 너무 깊게 들어갔습니다.
Plus it has thorns.
게다가 가시도 있어요.
If you pull it out violently
무리하게 잡아당기면
I'm afraid it will hurt my meridians.
내 경락에 상처를 줄까봐 두렵습니다.
And the blood will not stop flowing.
그리고 피의 흐름이 멈추지 않을 것입니다.
now
지금
You can only pierce the arrow's head. Come out carefully
화살의 머리만 뚫을 수 있습니다. 조심히 나오세요
I'm old.
나는 늙었다.
Hands are not steady, not daring to pierce
손이 안정되지 않고 감히 찌르지 못함
It's okay. I know medicine.
괜찮아요. 나는 의학을 안다.
Let me do it.
내가 해보자.
But this method is very painful.
하지만 이 방법은 매우 고통스럽습니다.
I'm afraid that this little lady won't be able to stand it.
이 작은 아가씨가 견딜 수 없을까 두렵습니다.
Ah Ying
아잉
The doctor said it would have to be drilled.
의사는 구멍을 뚫어야 한다고 말했습니다.
Take out the arrowhead.
화살촉을 꺼내세요.
It'll hurt a bit.
조금 아플 거예요.
Can you bear it?
견딜 수 있나요?
I'm there.
내가 거기있어.
You'll be fine.
괜찮아 질거야.
Mr. Kong, please endure the pain.
공씨님, 고통을 참아주세요.
Please bear with me.
양해해 주시기 바랍니다.
It'll be finished soon.
곧 끝날 거예요.
It's almost there.
거의 다 왔습니다.
Bite me, bite me
나를 물다, 나를 물다
nevermind
괜찮아요
It's okay now. It's okay.
이제 괜찮아요. 괜찮아요.
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
It's okay now.
이제 괜찮아요.
Let me help you wipe it.
닦을 수 있도록 도와드리겠습니다.
The valley's terrain is very dangerous.
계곡의 지형은 매우 위험합니다.
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
How many soldiers were the other side hiding?
상대방은 몇 명이나 숨어 있었나요?
One more thing
하나 더
The other party held a heavy crossbow.
상대방은 무거운 석궁을 들고 있었다.
You can survive.
당신은 살아남을 수 있습니다.
It is considered kindness.
친절로 간주됩니다.
The greatness that heaven has for you
하늘이 당신을 위해 가지고 있는 위대함
Shi Chi Lang
시치랑
Polite people will stay away from danger.
예의바른 사람은 위험을 피할 것이다.
You are a good general.
당신은 좋은 장군입니다.
Why did you imitate?
왜 흉내냈나요?
Your uncle died like that.
네 삼촌은 그렇게 돌아가셨어.
Just refer to textbooks.
그냥 교과서를 참고하세요.
Sit and discuss academics all day.
하루 종일 앉아서 학문에 대해 토론하십시오.
Just now, we had just attacked Dan Tong.
방금 우리는 Dan Tong을 공격했습니다.
according to plan
계획에 따라
It was an important moment in retaking the capital.
수도를 탈환하는 중요한 순간이었습니다.
If you have an accident
사고가 난 경우
What will you have me do?
나에게 무엇을 하라고 하시겠습니까?
One more thing
하나 더
The commander looked at that.
지휘관은 그 모습을 바라보았다.
She was a member of the Chui Family Army.
그녀는 추이 가문 군대의 일원이었습니다.
You will risk your life.
당신은 목숨을 걸게 될 것입니다.
Why to help her?
왜 그녀를 도와야합니까?
Who said I'm going to help?
내가 도와주겠다고 누가 말했어?
Mr. Kong He Kan
콩헤칸 씨
You can't...
당신은 할 수 없습니다 ...
I went to help Young Master Chui.
추이영사님을 도우러 갔습니다.
Do you think I believe you?
내가 당신을 믿을 것 같나요?
I think you believe
내 생각에는 당신이 믿는 것 같아요
okay
좋아요
Whatever you say is right.
당신이 말하는 것은 무엇이든 옳습니다.
You guys
너희들
No.
아니요.
You people, who are you?
여러분, 여러분은 누구입니까?
I couldn't imagine that Li Ni would dare to kill my younger brother.
리니가 감히 내 남동생을 죽일 거라고는 상상도 못했어요.
How dare he kill my salesman?
그 사람이 어떻게 감히 내 세일즈맨을 죽였나요?
Now I will kill you.
이제 나는 당신을 죽일 것입니다.
To atone for my brother's life
내 동생의 삶을 속죄하기 위해
Hu Yin
후인
I never thought that your child
네 아이가 그럴 거라고는 생각도 못 했어
Will you dare to kill my brother?
감히 내 동생을 죽일 셈이냐?
Now I will kill you.
이제 나는 당신을 죽일 것입니다.
Our men were able to stop Hu Yin Weiguo in time.
우리 병사들은 적시에 Hu Yin Weiguo를 막을 수있었습니다.
The Royal Doctor also knew what to say.
왕실 의사도 무슨 말을 해야 할지 알고 있었습니다.
Her Majesty trusts
폐하께서 신뢰하신다
The Viceroy arrived.
총독이 도착했습니다.
Viceroy, please punish me for my inability.
총독님, 저의 무능함을 벌해 주십시오.
Prince Liang was too frightened.
양 왕자는 너무 겁이났습니다.
His original pulse was already weak.
그의 원래 맥박은 이미 약했습니다.
Especially now
특히 지금은
Just now, it was because of Hu Yin's anger.
지금은 후인의 분노 때문이었습니다.
Can't breathe for a long time
오랫동안 숨을 쉴 수 없다
The heart nerve has broken.
심장 신경이 부러졌습니다.
Medicine and stone needles are not effective.
약이나 돌침은 효과가 없습니다.
Has passed away, please.
돌아가셨습니다.
I, I want to cut off his head.
나, 나는 그 사람의 머리를 자르고 싶다.
and sent it to his son
그리고 그것을 아들에게 보냈다.
Let his son have a taste.
아들에게 맛보게 해주세요.
What is it called? Pain like stabbing thorns
뭐라고 해요? 가시에 찔린 듯한 아픔
This person dies, no regrets.
이 사람은 죽어도 후회하지 않습니다.
Turn off the news
뉴스 꺼 줘
Take his bones and burn them.
그의 뼈를 가져다가 불태워라.
Destroy the bones.
뼈를 파괴하십시오.
Revenge for Zheng Guogong
정국공에 대한 복수
no
아니요
I want to cut off his head.
나는 그의 머리를 자르고 싶다.
and sent it to his son
그리고 그것을 아들에게 보냈다.
You hit me.
당신이 나를 때렸어요.
I didn't think that he would slap me.
나는 그가 나를 때릴 것이라고 생각하지 않았습니다.
Hu Yin Hu Yin
후인 후인
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
Duke Liang is dead.
양공이 죽었습니다.
what?
무엇?
Li Ni beheaded
리니 참수
Zheng Guogong's and sent it back.
Zheng Guogong이 그것을 돌려 보냈습니다.
Hu Yin Weiguo was so sad and angry that he couldn't stand it.
Hu Yin Weiguo는 너무 슬프고 화가 나서 참을 수 없었습니다.
Strangling Prince Liang to death
양왕을 목졸라 죽인다
Therefore, this news must be quickly suppressed.
그러므로 이 소식은 빨리 진압되어야 합니다.
Can't let Li Ni know.
리니에게 알리면 안 돼요.
that Prince Liang is dead
양 왕자가 죽었다고
I only know Hu Yin Weiguo.
나는 Hu Yin Weiguo만을 알고 있습니다.
Stupid and messy
멍청하고 지저분해
Unthinkable
상상할 수 없는
That she would ruin my big plans.
그녀가 내 큰 계획을 망칠 거라고요.
This Li Ni had an indomitable personality.
이 리니는 불굴의 성격을 가지고 있었습니다.
clever and cunning
영리하고 교활하다
Let Prince Liang still be alive.
양 왕자가 아직 살아있게 해주세요.
He didn't back down.
그는 물러서지 않았습니다.
Viceroy, don't get upset.
총독님, 화내지 마세요.
Marry a virtuous wife
현숙한 아내와 결혼하라
I married the wrong wife.
나는 잘못된 아내와 결혼했습니다.
to lose Luo Yang
뤄양을 잃다
Although this is the case
이런 경우에도 불구하고
Even if she makes another mistake
그녀가 또 다른 실수를 하더라도
Viceroy
총독
I never did anything to her.
나는 그녀에게 아무것도 한 적이 없습니다.
Probably the wife who shares the suffering
아마도 고통을 함께 나누는 아내일 것이다.
In the end, it is something different in your mind.
결국 그것은 당신의 마음 속에 있는 것이 다릅니다.
What are you again?
당신은 또 뭐죠?
She is your righteous wife.
그녀는 당신의 의로운 아내입니다.
I just don't like her.
나는 단지 그녀를 좋아하지 않습니다.
You know that in my heart
내 마음 속엔 너도 알잖아
My wife is only you.
내 아내는 당신뿐입니다.
Stop, stop, stop.
멈춰, 멈춰, 멈춰.
It's here.
여기 있어요.
Hurry and burn it.
서둘러서 태워버리세요.
Ordered from above
위에서 주문함
You have to break the bones and scatter them.
뼈를 부러뜨려 흩어버려야 합니다.
Please, please.
제발 제발.
Why is this so creepy?
이게 왜 이렇게 소름끼치는 걸까요?
yes
예
under both feet
두 발 아래
When this coffin was buried
이 관이 묻혔을 때
Yin energy is very strong.
음 에너지는 매우 강합니다.
Many people today in the palace
오늘 궁전에는 많은 사람들이 있다
Made a mistake and was dragged out.
실수를 해서 끌려나갔습니다.
All were beaten to death alive.
모두 산 채로 구타당해 사망했습니다.
So the villagers rumoured.
그래서 마을 사람들이 소문을 퍼뜨렸습니다.
that there is a devil haunting
악마가 맴돌고 있다는 걸
underfoot
발 밑에
The person who died today
오늘 죽은 사람
Wear beautiful robes
아름다운 예복을 입으세요
There are many types of silk clothes on the body.
몸에는 다양한 종류의 실크 옷이 있습니다.
Plus there are those shoes.
게다가 그 신발도 있어요.
Looking at it, I knew that it was very rich.
그것을 보니 매우 부자라는 것을 알았습니다.
You look.
당신은 보인다.
instead of burning it
태우는 대신
It's better not to sell it to us for money.
돈을 받고 우리에게 팔지 않는 것이 좋습니다.
Do you guys dare to make money even from dead people?
너희들은 죽은 사람에게서도 돈을 벌 수 있느냐?
No wonder there are people always spending money.
사람들이 항상 돈을 쓰는 것은 당연합니다.
wise
지혜로운
I really want this job.
나는 이 직업을 정말 원해요.
okay
좋아요
You guys make it a little nimble.
여러분, 좀 민첩하게 만드세요.
yes
예
Above has told me.
위에서는 나에게 말했다.
that he must be seen by us
그 사람을 우리가 봐야 한다고
burned to ashes with eyes
눈까지 타서 재가 됨
Both of you are invited.
두 분 모두 초대되었습니다.
Hurry and change.
서둘러서 바꿔보세요.
can
~할 수 있다
Hurry, hurry.
빨리 빨리.
Hurry and walk.
서둘러 걸어가세요.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
His Majesty
폐하
Has your body gotten better?
몸은 좋아졌나요?
I'm not the eldest child. If you kill your father
나는 큰 아이가 아닙니다. 아버지를 죽이면
I must thank you for being emperor.
황제가 되어주셔서 감사해야 합니다.
Is this what you wrote?
이게 당신이 쓴 글인가요?
yes
예
His Majesty
폐하
You ungrateful son.
배은망덕한 아들아.
You are an ungrateful son.
당신은 배은망덕한 아들입니다.
Are you really going to kill your father?
정말 아버지를 죽이실 겁니까?
Viceroy Sun was so cruel.
Sun 총독은 너무 잔인했습니다.
You still want to be emperor.
당신은 여전히 ​​황제가되고 싶어합니다.
You really want to kill me.
당신은 정말로 나를 죽이고 싶어합니다.
His Majesty
폐하
That was just a plan.
그것은 단지 계획이었습니다.
Just provoke Sun Jing.
그냥 Sun Jing을 자극하세요.
in order to help His Majesty come out
폐하께서 나오시도록 돕기 위해
Help me out.
도와주세요.
Where is this?
여긴 어디야?
This is Dan Tong.
단통입니다.
After Sun Jing rebelled,
손징이 반란을 일으킨 후
Father also
아버지도
locked up as a hostage I've always been in the capital.
인질로 갇혀서 나는 항상 수도에 있었습니다.
I'm always planning.
나는 항상 계획을 세우고 있습니다.
How to help Father come out
아버지가 나오도록 돕는 방법
previous
이전의
Arrange manpower secretly
인력을 비밀리에 배치하다
in the palace
궁전에서
through the Chui Sakul Army
추이사쿨군을 통해
Just wait when the opportunity arises to take action.
조치를 취할 기회가 생길 때까지 기다리십시오.
Well, when the opportunity arose, I took action.
글쎄, 기회가 생겼을 때 나는 조치를 취했습니다.
Plan to act when your opportunity arises.
기회가 생기면 행동할 계획을 세우십시오.
is to send an ungrateful letter
배은망덕한 편지를 보내는 것입니다
Are you going to give it to Sun Jing?
Sun Jing에게 줄 건가요?
You know.
알잖아.
If Sun Jing changed his mind just a little,
쑨징이 조금만 마음을 바꾸면
I'd probably have my head cut off.
아마 머리가 잘렸을 겁니다.
His Majesty
폐하
I know that after you saw the letter
그 편지를 보고 나서야 알았어
Must be extremely angry
극도로 화가 났나봐
Your body has always been bad.
당신의 몸은 항상 나빴습니다.
Often dizzy
종종 어지러움
I want you to be very angry.
나는 당신이 매우 화를 내기를 바랍니다.
You will immediately faint.
당신은 즉시 기절할 것이다.
I ordered the drug user to fake death.
나는 마약 사용자에게 가짜 죽음을 명령했습니다.
Makes his father look like he's dead. to fool Sun Jing
그의 아버지가 죽은 것처럼 보이게 만듭니다. Sun Jing을 속이기 위해
Waiting for the body to be put in the coffin
시신이 관에 들어갈 때까지 기다리고 있습니다.
Let the lily tree die instead of the peach tree.
복숭아나무 대신 백합나무가 죽게 해주세요.
Then help Father come out.
그럼 아버지가 나오도록 도와주세요.
You are ungrateful.
당신은 배은망덕합니다.
You are an ungrateful son.
당신은 배은망덕한 아들입니다.
You act rashly and without thinking.
당신은 성급하고 생각 없이 행동합니다.
You are taking your life.
당신은 당신의 생명을 빼앗고 있습니다.
of the father at birth
태어날 때 아버지의
Become a bet, did you know?
내기가 되세요, 알고 계셨나요?
I don't dare.
감히 그럴 수가 없어요.
What else do you not dare to do?
또 무엇을 감히 할 수 없습니까?
I saw your face and I was angry.
나는 당신의 얼굴을 보고 화가 났습니다.
Get over it.
극복하세요.
Hurry and get rid of your head.
어서 머리를 치우세요.
Yes, my child asks for leave.
네, 제 아이가 휴가를 요청합니다.
Waiting for Father to stop being angry.
아버지가 화를 멈추기를 기다립니다.
I will come to visit you again.
나는 다시 당신을 방문할 것입니다.
Hurry and get rid of your head.
어서 머리를 치우세요.
Saluting the general
장군님께 경의를 표하는
I heard that Prince Liang has returned.
양왕자가 돌아왔다는 소식을 들었습니다.
So I stewed a cup of chicken curry with pine mushrooms.
그래서 송이버섯을 넣은 치킨 카레 한 컵을 끓였습니다.
Scoop out the oil.
기름을 퍼내세요.
Make it a clear soup.
맑은 국물로 만들어주세요.
I think Prince Liang
내 생각에는 양왕자가
Going through hardships Tired both physically and mentally
고난을 겪으면서 육체적으로나 정신적으로 지쳤습니다
Eat light, nourishing food.
가볍고 영양가 있는 음식을 섭취하세요.
Can restore breath
호흡을 회복할 수 있다
Grandson probably doesn't know.
손자는 아마 모를 거예요.
Our young lady
우리 아가씨
Watch over the stove by yourself.
난로를 직접 살펴보세요.
Stewed for many hours
여러 시간 동안 끓인
Qiu Shui had already said too much.
Qiu Shui는 이미 너무 많은 말을 했습니다.
It's difficult for you to get a loan.
대출을 받기가 어렵습니다.
What are these words, General?
장군님, 이 말은 무엇입니까?
The general is a person who has to do big things.
장군은 큰 일을 해야 하는 사람이다.
Busy with military activities
군사활동으로 바쁜
Sow Wattle is incompetent.
Sow Wattle은 무능합니다.
And still a weak woman
그리고 여전히 약한 여자
Adding to the suffering of the army
군대의 고통을 더하다
Since Prince Liang has returned
양왕이 돌아온 이후
I asked the general to allow me to sow the wattles and take care of him.
나는 장군에게 와틀을 심고 그를 돌볼 수 있도록 허락해 달라고 부탁했습니다.
Prince Liang's clothes and food.
양왕의 옷과 음식.
this
이것
It's better not to disturb Mr. Noo Loan.
누론씨를 방해하지 않는 것이 좋습니다.
His father had just been rescued.
그의 아버지는 방금 구출되었습니다.
My mind is still not stable.
아직 마음이 안정되지 않았습니다.
Mood The mood was not good.
기분 기분이 좋지 않았습니다.
General, don't worry.
장군님, 걱정하지 마세요.
Sow wattles at home
집에서 와틀을 뿌리다
I used to take care of the elderly.
나는 노인들을 돌보곤 했습니다.
I know that my body is not good.
몸이 안 좋은 건 나도 안다.
suffering from illness
질병으로 고통받고 있다
It's normal to be in a bad mood.
기분이 좋지 않은 것은 정상입니다.
Commander, please rest assured.
지휘관님, 안심하세요.
Wan Niang will take care of Prince Liang.
Wan Niang은 Liang 왕자를 돌볼 것입니다.
Definitely very good
확실히 아주 좋아요
Yes, sir.
알겠습니다.
Our young lady is a detailed person.
우리 아가씨는 세심한 사람이에요.
At that time our master was sick.
그 때 우리 주인님이 아프셨습니다.
All of them are women who help take care of him.
그들 모두는 그를 돌보는 데 도움을 주는 여성들이다.
Ask the general
장군에게 물어보세요
You can use it to sow wattles. What little abilities do you have?
그것을 사용하여 와틀을 심을 수 있습니다. 당신은 어떤 작은 능력을 가지고 있습니까?
Like that, it's bothering you already.
그런 식으로 이미 당신을 괴롭히고 있습니다.
Lady Taozi
레이디 타오지
Has your wound gotten better?
상처는 좀 나아졌나요?
It's not a big deal.
그것은 큰 문제가 아니다.
At most, it only hurt for a few days.
기껏해야 며칠 동안만 아팠을 뿐입니다.
You must be hungry. Let's eat something.
배가 고프겠군요. 뭔가 좀 먹자.
come
오다
can
~할 수 있다
What's the matter? Aren't the noodles delicious?
무슨 일이야? 국수 맛있지 않아요?
How can water noodles be more delicious than pig ears?
물국수가 어떻게 돼지귀보다 맛있을 수 있나요?
What are you laughing at?
당신은 무엇을 웃고 있습니까?
There's nothing.
아무것도 없습니다.
Mee is almost cold. You hurry up and eat.
Mee는 거의 추워요. 너 얼른 가서 먹어.
(General's quarters)
(장군 숙소)
What are you doing secretly?
몰래 뭐하는 거야?
Do you want to secretly kiss me?
나한테 몰래 키스할래?
Do you have anything worthy of me secretly kissing?
내가 몰래 키스할 만한 가치가 있는 게 있나요?
This one.
이 하나.
I saved your life.
나는 당신의 생명을 구했습니다.
You think I helped you.
내가 당신을 도왔다고 생각하는군요.
How many times?
몇 번이나?
You act inconsiderate.
당신은 배려심 없는 행동을 합니다.
A benefactor who saved your life like this?
이렇게 목숨을 구해준 은인이요?
Grandson trusts
손자가 신뢰한다
What day will you be in danger?
어느 날 당신이 위험에 처하게 될까요?
I must eliminate all difficulties.
나는 모든 어려움을 제거해야합니다.
Break through the thorns to help you.
당신을 돕기 위해 가시를 뚫고 나오세요.
Polite people keep the truth. How delighted
예의바른 사람은 진실을 지킨다. 얼마나 기뻤는지
How do you know?
어떻게 알 수 있나요?
That someone wants to secretly attack us.
누군가가 우리를 몰래 공격하고 싶어한다는 것입니다.
I know Luoyang
나는 낙양을 안다
Send out some troops.
병력을 좀 보내세요.
And this force held the crossbow.
그리고 이 힘이 석궁을 쥐고 있었습니다.
Clearly wanted to assassinate
분명히 암살하고 싶었어
I thought about it.
나는 그것에 대해 생각했다.
I suddenly thought of your Chui clan army.
갑자기 추이족 군대가 생각났어요.
That Chui Li
그 추이 리
He had come to discuss with Pei Yuan.
그는 Pei Yuan과 논의하기 위해 왔습니다.
will secretly attack Khun Chai Chui
비밀리에 Khun Chai Chui를 공격합니다
I think
제 생각에는
That Chui Li probably wouldn't.
Chui Li는 아마도 그렇지 않을 것입니다.
Go do it with someone else.
가서 다른 사람이랑 해보세요.
But go do it with Mr. Chui
하지만 가서 Mr. Chui와 함께 해보세요
Yes, Chui Li.
응, 추이 리.
It must be him.
그 사람임에 틀림없어요.
And I don't know.
그리고 나는 모른다.
What method does he use?
그는 어떤 방법을 사용합니까?
that can give the people of Luoyang
낙양 사람들에게 줄 수 있는 것은
Let him borrow your troops.
그에게 당신의 군대를 빌려주세요.
Since Chui Li wanted to kill Young Master Chui
추이 리가 추이 스승을 죽이고 싶었기 때문에
So you have to find someone.
그래서 누군가를 찾아야 합니다.
Let's blame him for the murder.
살인에 대해 그를 비난합시다.
During this time, I am at Dan Tong.
이 기간 동안 저는 Dan Tong에 있습니다.
and was the commander of the Zhenxi Army.
그리고 Zhenxi 군대의 사령관이었습니다.
Not the best option
최선의 선택은 아니다
expected
예상되는
He probably used this method.
그는 아마도 이 방법을 사용했을 것이다.
Go convince my elder brother to borrow some troops.
가서 내 형에게 군대를 빌리도록 설득해 보세요.
Your big brother?
당신의 큰 형?
I couldn't imagine that they would do this.
나는 그들이 이것을 할 것이라고 상상할 수 없었습니다.
They are stupid and fuzzy.
그들은 어리 석고 모호합니다.
It's normal to be easily deceived by people.
사람들이 쉽게 속는 것은 정상입니다.
The world is like this.
세상은 이렇습니다.
Chui Li was just
추이 리(Chui Li)는 단지
Cousin of Aren't you all sirs?
사촌 여러분은 모두 선생님이 아니신가요?
It is a quarrel between siblings.
형제자매간의 다툼입니다.
It's definitely not good.
확실히 좋지 않습니다.
Things in Yingzhou must have secrets.
Yingzhou의 모든 것에는 비밀이 있을 것입니다.
What about you, sir? What about Taozi?
당신은 어떻습니까? 도자는 어떻습니까?
Are they injured?
부상을 입었나요?
And where is my horse?
내 말은 어디에 있나요?
You probably can't.
당신은 아마 할 수 없습니다.
I'll hurry back to Yingzhou now.
이제 서둘러 잉저우로 돌아갈게요.
I'm worried.
걱정된다.
Yingzhou is
잉저우는
The base of our Chui clan army.
우리 추이족 군대의 기지입니다.
Not working
작동 안함
I'll have to think of a way to hurry back.
빨리 돌아갈 방법을 생각해 봐야 할 것 같아요.
Ah Ying
아잉
Your injuries are not fatal.
당신의 부상은 치명적이지 않습니다.
But your gentleman
하지만 당신의 신사
May need to be rehabilitated well
잘 재활해야 할 수도 있습니다
It's been several days.
며칠이 지났습니다.
If you insist on rushing back
굳이 빨리 돌아가라고 하면
I will not hinder you.
나는 당신을 방해하지 않을 것입니다.
But you must think carefully.
하지만 잘 생각해 보아야 합니다.
that you can
당신이 할 수 있다는
endured until meeting a large army
큰 군대를 만날 때까지 버텼다
And there's still strength left.
그리고 아직 힘이 남아있습니다.
Go help Ying Zhou again or not?
가서 Ying Zhou를 다시 도와줄까요, 말까요?
Don't hurry.
서두르지 마세요.
The matter has reached this stage.
문제가 이 단계에 이르렀습니다.
Don't fight us, let's think.
싸우지 말고 생각해보자.
Is there any other way?
다른 방법이 있나요?
sir
선생님
Sir, you have recovered.
선생님, 회복되셨습니다.
What about Aing?
아잉은 어떻습니까?
Khun Chai trusts
차이쿤은 신뢰한다
The captain is fine.
선장은 괜찮습니다.
Only minor injuries
경미한 부상만
It's not a big deal.
그것은 큰 문제가 아니다.
Then that's good.
그렇다면 좋습니다.
Ah, what?
아, 뭐?
sir
선생님
Ah, things are gone.
아, 물건이 없어졌네요.
Don't be sad.
슬퍼하지 마세요.
protect sir
선생님을 보호하세요
It's our duty.
그것은 우리의 의무입니다.
But now
그러나 지금
Ah, things no longer exist.
아, 더 이상 존재하지 않습니다.
Ah, things really no longer exist.
아, 정말 더 이상 존재하지 않는 것 같아요.
sir
선생님
Ah, things I probably didn't want. This gentleman is sad like this.
아, 아마 내가 원하지 않았던 일들. 이 신사는 이렇게 슬프다.
Me and Uncle Thing
나와 삼촌 것
They were all orphans that no one wanted.
그들은 모두 누구도 원하지 않는 고아였습니다.
If you don't have Mr.
미스터가 없다면
with the captain who received us
우리를 받아준 선장과 함께
Let us be in the Chui clan army.
추이족 군대에 들어가자.
And where is there for us to live?
그러면 우리가 살 수 있는 곳은 어디입니까?
I died for you.
나는 당신을 위해 죽었습니다.
Ah, definitely no regrets.
아, 절대 후회하지 않습니다.
I don't regret it either.
나도 후회하지 않는다.
I cannot allow you to say these words.
나는 당신이 이런 말을 하는 것을 허락할 수 없습니다.
Where is this?
여긴 어디야?
Dan Tong
그리고 배럴
Zhenxi army camp
진시군 캠프
He is Dali's grandson.
그는 달리의 손자입니다.
Yes, it was him who brought us back.
그렇다, 우리를 다시 데려온 사람은 바로 그 사람이었다.
Li Ni
리니
sir
선생님
You should rest first.
먼저 쉬어야 해요.
Just now, Tao Zi came to take the young man's pulse.
바로 지금 도자가 청년의 맥박을 재러 왔습니다.
Military doctor of the Zhenxi army
진시군 군의관
I came to see your condition.
나는 당신의 상태를 보러 왔습니다.
Said that the young man was seriously injured.
그 청년은 심각한 부상을 입었다고 합니다.
Must rest a lot.
많이 쉬어야 합니다.
no
아니요
I can't stay here.
나는 여기에 머물 수 없습니다.
sir
선생님
Urgent matters change according to the situation.
긴급사항은 상황에 따라 변경됩니다.
We have to recover well first.
먼저 잘 회복해야 합니다.
Plan again
다시 계획하다
This place was still thousands of li away from Yingzhou.
이곳은 영주에서 아직 수천 리 떨어져 있었습니다.
If a man doesn't take care of himself well
남자가 자기 관리를 잘 안 하면
That's destruction.
그것은 파괴입니다.
Placing all our pieces
우리의 모든 조각을 배치
There is another matter.
또 다른 문제가 있습니다.
Chen thing
첸 것
And the soldiers who fought to the death
그리고 목숨을 걸고 싸운 군인들
of the Chui Sakul Army
추이사쿨군 소속
Please disturb my grandson and send someone to help me.
내 손자를 방해하고 나를 도와줄 사람을 보내주세요.
bury them
그들을 묻어라
You trust me.
당신은 나를 신뢰합니다.
When you still haven't recovered
아직 회복되지 않았을 때
I've sent someone to collect the corpse.
시체를 수거할 사람을 보냈어요.
A soldier from the Chui army who fought until the death.
죽을 때까지 싸운 추이군 병사.
I know that Chen things
나도 첸의 일을 알고 있어
Be the bodyguard at your prince's side.
왕자 옆에서 경호원이 되어 보세요.
I've ordered people to go make spirit signs.
나는 사람들에게 영혼의 표식을 만들라고 명령했습니다.
Waiting for Mr. Chui to recover well.
추이씨의 쾌유를 기다립니다.
Gradually go and pay homage by yourself.
점차적으로 가서 스스로 경의를 표하십시오.
Aing, I'm sorry.
아잉, 미안해요.
thank you
감사합니다
come
오다
When recovered
회복되었을 때
You should be able to take medicine.
약을 복용할 수 있어야 합니다.
Taozi ordered me repeatedly.
Taozi는 나에게 반복해서 명령했습니다.
Let me keep an eye on you taking medicine.
약을 복용하는 모습을 지켜보겠습니다.
In order to prevent the wound from becoming pus-filled
상처에 고름이 차는 것을 방지하기 위해
Very bitter
매우 쓴맛
Lady Taozi
레이디 타오지
I'm about to go find you.
나는 당신을 찾으러 갈 예정입니다.
What a coincidence!
이런 우연이!
I'm about to go find it as well.
나도 찾으러 갈 예정이다.
What is the matter with you?
당신에게 무슨 문제가 있습니까?
This is a painkiller.
이것은 진통제입니다.
that I found for you
내가 당신을 위해 찾아낸 것
You used it to put on wounds.
상처를 입히는 데 사용했지요.
This way, you won't get hurt anymore.
이렇게 하면 더 이상 상처받지 않을 것입니다.
fool
바보
Have you forgotten?
너는 잊었 니?
that I can administer the medicine myself
내가 직접 약을 투여할 수 있다는 것
I definitely haven't forgotten.
나는 확실히 잊지 않았습니다.
just
단지
I'm just afraid that if you don't exist,
난 단지 당신이 존재하지 않는다면,
Last time you said
지난번에 네가 말했지
Aren't your wounds going to hurt for many days?
네 상처가 여러 날 동안 아플 것 같지 않느냐?
Yes, then I will accept it.
네, 그럼 받아들이겠습니다.
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
What is the matter with you?
당신에게 무슨 문제가 있습니까?
I'm looking for you.
나는 당신을 찾고 있어요.
Because I want you to help me.
왜냐하면 나는 당신이 나를 도와주기를 바라기 때문입니다.
What do you want me to do for you?
내가 당신에게 무엇을 해주기를 바라나요?
just tell
그냥 말해
I'll definitely help.
내가 꼭 도와줄게.
Do you guys have any sugar?
여러분, 설탕 있어요?
If it were honey
꿀이었다면
It'll be even better.
더욱 좋아질 것입니다.
sugar or
설탕이나
We fight and fight.
우리는 싸우고 또 싸웁니다.
in the kitchen
부엌에서
How can there be sugar?
어떻게 설탕이 있을 수 있나요?
No need to mention honey at all.
꿀은 전혀 말할 필요가 없습니다.
What do you want sugar for?
무엇 때문에 설탕을 원하시나요?
our captain
우리 선장
Since I was little, after taking medicine
어렸을 때부터 약을 먹고 나서
I won't eat rice.
나는 밥을 먹지 않을 것이다.
At that time, if there was sugar
그때 설탕이 있었다면
After taking the medicine
약을 복용한 후
Give her sweet water to drink.
그녀에게 단 물을 마시게 하세요.
She's going to eat rice.
그녀는 밥을 먹을 거예요.
But there's no market nearby.
그런데 근처에 시장이 없어요.
There is nowhere to buy.
살 곳이 없습니다.
Prince Liang had reached Dan Tong safely.
양왕은 무사히 단통에 도착했다.
Hopefully the grandson and heir to the throne will be able to Change bad things into good things.
손자와 왕위 계승자가 나쁜 일을 좋은 일로 바꿀 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Free from misfortune
불행에서 벗어나다
Her Majesty trusts
폐하께서 신뢰하신다
The grandson and heir to the throne must be safe.
손자와 왕위 계승자는 안전해야 합니다.
Li Ni had captured Dan Tong.
Li Ni는 Dan Tong을 점령했습니다.
It is expected that Sun Jing
Sun Jing이 예상됩니다.
The mind must be distraught.
마음이 혼란스러워야합니다.
You look.
당신은 보인다.
Today he had orders to harvest rice.
오늘 그는 쌀을 수확하라는 명령을 받았습니다.
to the people in the city
도시의 사람들에게
Every family hoards
모든 가족은 비축합니다
enough food to eat for three months
3개월 동안 먹을 수 있는 식량
Sun Jing seemed to be preparing.
순진이 준비하고 있는 것 같았어요.
For being surrounded
둘러싸여 있어서
Thus, the seventeen grandchildren
그리하여 열일곱 명의 손자들이
Will he lead an army to surround the city?
그는 군대를 이끌고 도시를 포위할 것인가?
Xichang City had a strong moat.
시창시는 강한 해자를 갖고 있었습니다.
Easy to defend but difficult to attack.
방어하기는 쉽지만 공격하기는 어렵습니다.
Li Ni would definitely not force his way in.
Li Ni는 확실히 자신의 길을 강요하지 않을 것입니다.
hope
희망
Before Sun Jing
쑨징 전
will call back the great army
큰 군대를 다시 불러올 것이다
Li Ni would be able to save Xichang City.
Li Ni는 Xichang City를 구할 수 있습니다.
Where have you gone and what have you done?
어디로 갔으며 무엇을 했나요?
I didn't even eat lunch.
나는 점심도 먹지 않았다.
I just went for a walk on the mountain.
방금 산에 산책하러 갔어요.
Shi Chi Lang
시치랑
You are now a commander. of the Zhenxi Army
이제 당신은 지휘관이 되었습니다. 진시군 소속
No matter what you do
당신이 뭘 하든지
This cannot be done arbitrarily.
이는 임의로 수행할 수 없습니다.
Just like this time
이번처럼
You didn't care about the danger and went to help General He.
당신은 위험을 개의치 않고 헤 장군을 도우러 나섰습니다.
Captain He is clever and cunning.
캡틴 그는 영리하고 교활합니다.
and was extremely loyal to Cuilin.
Cuilin에게 매우 충성 스러웠습니다.
A person like this will become a person sooner or later.
이런 사람은 조만간 사람이 될 것입니다.
It's definitely our downfall.
그것은 확실히 우리의 몰락이다.
I think
제 생각에는
She was more loyal to Cui Yi.
그녀는 Cui Yi에게 더 충실했습니다.
Do you think that
당신은 그렇게 생각합니까?
Between her and Mr. Chui
그녀와 추이씨 사이
How strange is that?
얼마나 이상합니까?
What's strange?
뭐가 이상해요?
That Captain He was loyal to Chui Lin.
그 선장은 Chui Lin에게 충성스러웠습니다.
Or is he loyal to Cui Yi?
아니면 그는 Cui Yi에게 충성하는 걸까요?
It's the same.
그것은 동일합니다.
Father and son are like the same person.
아버지와 아들은 같은 사람이다.
There are words that I shouldn't say.
해서는 안 될 말이 있습니다.
But if
하지만 만약
I'm not talking to you.
너 한테 이야기 하는게 아니야.
No one is talking to you anymore.
더 이상 아무도 당신에게 말을 걸지 않습니다.
Passionate, intoxicated, insane
열광적인, 술에 취한, 미친
It is not the act of a polite person.
예의바른 사람의 행동이 아닙니다.
You've misunderstood.
당신은 오해했습니다.
It's not what you think.
그것은 당신이 생각하는 것과 다릅니다.
Shi Qi Lang, you look.
Shi Qi Lang, 보세요.
I'm prepared.
나는 준비됐다.
I'll come back and talk to you soon.
곧 돌아와서 얘기하겠습니다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
I won't tell you.
나는 당신에게 말하지 않을 것입니다.
♪If you forget the fleeting light of fireflies♪
♪반딧불이의 덧없는 빛을 잊으신다면♪
♪Waiting for memories♪
♪추억을 기다리며♪
♪Shattered and drowned♪
♪부서지고 익사했어요♪
♪Settled on the stain on your heart♪
♪마음의 얼룩에 안착♪
♪That connection♪
♪그 인연♪
♪This is something I'm having a hard time letting go of♪
♪이건 정말 버릴 수 없는 일이에요♪
♪If the anxiety never fades♪
♪불안이 결코 사라지지 않는다면♪
♪Return to the first time with regret♪
♪후회하며 처음으로 돌아가자♪
♪The warmth that fate once had♪
♪운명이 가졌던 따뜻함♪
♪I want to keep it for you♪
♪당신을 위해 간직하고 싶어요♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪사랑이 기억한다면♪
♪We made a promise♪
♪우리 약속했어요♪
♪Even if this love hurts me♪
♪이 사랑이 나를 아프게 해도♪
♪I will live for you♪
♪당신을 위해 살게요♪
♪Follow the outline in your memories♪
♪기억 속의 개요를 따라가 보세요♪
♪Waiting for the person I cling to♪
♪꼭 붙어있는 사람을 기다리고 있어요♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪사랑이 기억한다면♪
♪Promises kept for you♪
♪당신을 위한 약속은 지켜집니다♪
♪Change of cause and effect♪
♪원인과 결과의 변화♪
♪I don't regret standing up for you♪
♪당신을 위해 일어선 것을 후회하지 않습니다♪
♪I give up my desire for you♪
♪당신에 대한 욕망을 포기합니다♪
♪Always waiting for you to answer me♪
♪항상 당신의 대답을 기다리고 있어요♪
♪If love remembers♪
♪사랑이 기억한다면♪
♪Promises kept for you♪
♪당신을 위한 약속은 지켜집니다♪
♪Change of cause and effect♪
♪원인과 결과의 변화♪
♪I don't regret standing up for you♪
♪당신을 위해 일어선 것을 후회하지 않습니다♪
♪I give up my desire for you♪
♪당신에 대한 욕망을 포기합니다♪
♪Always waiting for you to answer me♪
♪항상 당신의 대답을 기다리고 있어요♪